<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mia Soto</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mia Soto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Python and RStudio Interaction</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/python-and-rstudio-interaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/python-and-rstudio-interaction/</guid>
      <description>Python and RStudio can execute very similar functions. These fucntions, while the syntax to execute them is somewaht similar, can be executed separately or interact with one another. This similarity will be explored in this blog post.  ##Calculator
10-3 ## 7 10+3 ## 13 10*3 ## 30 pow(10,3) ## 1000 10/3 ## 3.3333333333333335 The chunk of code above demonstrates the similarities and differences between Python and R when using the languages as a calculator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Secret Shrimp Pasta Recipe</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/super-secret-shrimp-pasta-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/super-secret-shrimp-pasta-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Since the COIVD-19 pandemic, I have worked tirelessly to find hobbies that excite me. I have always been into cooking; however, when quarantine hit, I really made an effort to expand my knowledge about food beyond simple recipes. This passion carried on into this school year, especially because I had my own kitchen to experiment in. In this blog I will share with you what I believe to be the best and easiest shrimp pasta recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Mia Soto eid:mis696  Introduction This data set contains data from car crashes. There are 15 variables in this data set with 26,217 observations, and I will discuss the most notable variables. The first notable variable is a categorical variable called dead that classifies the victim of the crash as alive or dead. Two other important variables are airbag and seatbelt, which are two categorical variables with the option none or airbag/belted, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Mia Soto eid:mis696  Introduction I chose to use personal data for this project as I would love to see how this class can apply to an analysis of my daily life. The two data sets I used were Netflix viewing data and Apple Watch workout statistics. The Netflix viewing data for the year of 2020 was requested from Netflix for my account. Then, I took the data and altered it to make it more fitting for the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Resume</title>
      <link>/academicresume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/academicresume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Resume</title>
      <link>/professionalresume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/professionalresume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my resumes below:
 Professional Resume
 Academic Resume
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
